tracer here
she is nice the Cavalry's here that's my
line think I could have a look at one of
those bombs of yours over my dead body
lucio I'll race ya oh you're on
Hecuba then stay out of our way
on you born wearing all that yes but is
too late to change
chase' you're so amazing you inspire me
Mae you're the real hero
you're so lucky tracer ever since I was
a little girl I dreamed of joining
overwatch maybe you'll still get your
chance who knows what the future holds
slow down think about your actions okay
dad
sometimes I feel a little sick after
using my translocator I'm sure you know
what I mean tracer what be a problem if
you just disappear forever
don't think I don't recognize that
device of yours I know you stole it what
can I say
a girl just has to have the latest tech
whoa it's me it's my chronal accelerator
malfunctioning again wait that's what I
was just thinking spooky
what you looking at an annoyance
Sancia it looks like we will be working
together don't think I'm happy about
that oh so predictable even when you
reverse time you always make the same
decisions don't be so sure about that
Oh Winston got you favor for the last
time no more bananas
Winston you're an animal
empirical evidence suggests I'm a real
animal
need any adjustments to your chrono
accelerator I think just kidding Winston
it works great
Wow it's an honor to me a member of the
Shambhala Mont data was an inspiration
to me to us all
I miss him greatly
sorry cap
Death Comes
no one likes a thief squished
that felt good
sorry big guy
it was Beauty killed the Beast
oh sorry Santa
you could be my wingman anytime Haho
nice one Reinhardt
Winston you're an animal